## **ABEERA M**

# Python Full-Stack Developer





+91 9400576876



abeeraazees@gmail.com



Calicut

#### **EDUCATION**

2012-2016

#### **Calicut University**

B-tech CSE

AWH Engineering College 72%

2010-2012

## Kerala Department of Higher Secondary Education

Meppayur Salafi Higher Secondary School 85%

2009-2010

**CBSE** 

Grace Public School 80%

#### HARD SKILLS

- Python
- JavaScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- JQuery
- Android
- REST API
- ANGULAR
- MySQL
- Manual Testing
- Selenium

#### **ABOUT ME**

To Leverage my expertise as a full stack developer with Python-Django with an Internship and bridge my career gap by contributing my skills and knowledge to an organization that values innovation, creativity and continous learning, while also allowing me to grow and advance my career.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Software Tester Trainee**

Rogersoft (2016-2017)

- Utilized tools such as Selenium and QTP to test web applications on various browsers and devices.
- Performed Automation Testing on web-based Applications.
- Executed manual test cases to ensure the functionality and usability of web applications.
- Used Jira as a project tracking tool

#### **Python Full-Stack Developer Intern**

Maxlore Innovations (2022-2023)

- Undertook role as a full-stack developer working across back-end programming using Python-Django and front-end development with Bootstrap-HTML.CSS...
- Build an online plant nursery site from scratch.
- Designed clone sites of Facebook and Instagram.

## WORKSHOPS AND COURSES ATTENDED

ROGERSOFT SOFTWARE TRAINING CENTRE(05/2017)

Manual and Automation Testing (SELENIUM AND QTP)

INFOSYS(04/2016)

Campus Connect Program

IPSR SOLUTIONS LIMITED(02/2016)

INTRODUCTION TO CLOUD

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Flexibility
- Team Work

#### **LANGUAGES**

**ENGLISH** 

Full professional proficiency

MALAYALAM

Full professional proficiency

HINDI

Limited Working Proficiency

#### **CERTIFICATES**

ISTQB FOUNDATIONAL LEVEL CERTIFIED (04/2017)